

MIKE KUZIN

Graphic & Web Developer

- 100 Valley Stream Dr, Apt 2A Delmont, PA 15626
- 724.575.0989
- info@mikekuzin.com
- □ mikekuzin.com

OBJECTIVE

To join a top-notch team of designers and developers with the goal of delivering cutting-edge user interface designs and successful production-ready front-end code.

To Apply W3C web standards with great skill and craftsmanship in achieving the best cross-browser user experience for the sake of long-term user retention and engagement.

EDUCATION

The Art Institute of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA Received a Bachelor of Science in Graphic Design. Graduated in December 2008.

SPECIALTIES

Skills

Front-End Development, CMS Integration (Drupal, WordPress, Custom Solutions), Art Direction, Photo Retouching, Corporate Identity, Packaging Graphics, Logo Design, Page Layout, Print Production

Languages

JavaScript, CSS, HTML, XHTML, DOM, PHP, jQuery, Mootools

Operating Systems

Mac OS X, UNIX, Linux, Microsoft Windows

Software

Adobe Creative Suite, QuarkXPress, FTP & SSH Software, Coda, Espresso, CSSEdit, Microsoft Office

■ PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Direct Axis Creative, Pittsburgh, PA March 2009 – April 2010

Graphic Designer & Front End Developer

Held an associative role, creating campaigns to support corporate and non-profit brands such as: Philips, Pitt Athletics, Davis & Elkins College, Pittsburgh Technical Institute, Law Offices of Attorney G. Handelsman, Island Automotive Group, MCN Salon, etc. Responsibilities included: handling client relations, balancing multiple projects while meeting deadlines, development of various print media and web campaigns, server maintenance and troubleshooting, technical software & hardware support for the office.

Edgar Snyder & Associates, Pittsburgh, PA January 2009 – March 2009 Graphic Design Intern

Responsible for maintaining brand identity whilst updating outdoor and print-media campaigns. Creation of new web, media, and print materials under the lead of a creative director.



MIKE KUZIN Graphic & Web Developer

- 100 Valley Stream Dr, Apt 2A Delmont, PA 15626
- 724.575.0989
- info@mikekuzin.com
- □ mikekuzin.com

The Art Institute of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA

April 2008 - January 2009

Graphic Design Intern

Designer/Illustrator on several projects, including creation of banners to be hung in conjunction with the Pittsburgh 250! celebration and a promotional calendar for the Art Institute of Pittsburgh.

KUZIN Design, Pittsburgh, PA April 2006 – Present **Sole Proprietor**

Performed print & web contract work for small business and working professionals. Met one-on-one with clients in exploring the best possible options for their web or print presence. Handled duties ranging from creative design to code implementation.

AWARDS AND DISTINCTIONS

Employers Choice Award | December 2009 Best of Show Award | December 2009 Student of the Quarter | Fall 2008 Art Institute of Pittsburgh Honors and Deans List | 2006 – 2008

Artwork exhibited in Art Institute Student Show | 2008 Selected for Honors Design Studio | 2008

■ PROJECTS AND ONLINE PRESENCE

My Design Portfolio http://mikekuzin.com My Blog http://mikekuzin.com/blog Twitter http://twitter.com/kuzin LinkedIn http://linkedin.com/in/michaelkuzin

References, code samples, and portfolio available upon request.

A permanent copy of this resume is available at mikekuzin.com/resume.pdf